This is the Realm of Magic.
It's called so because magic
is a natural part of people's life here.
They can fly with a broom,
levitate heavy objects,
or even make something out of thin air.
In this world,
people can use magic at will,
and magic has become
a regular part in their daily life.
People believe that
their magic is a gift given by god.
And one's level of magic
can even determine their social status.
In this world where dragons
are flying in the sky,
there is a remote forest.
And deep in the forest, there is a man
who doesn't fit in
with the rest of the world.
There's nothing like cream puff
after some exercise.
MASHLE: MAGIC AND MUSCLES
My name is Regro Burnedead.
My son and I live alone
in this remote forest.
I'm a chic and elegant 75-year-old man.
REGRO BURNEDEAD
I've done reckless things
when I was young.
But when I get to this age,
not much can bother me anymore.
If you ask me why,
it's my whole life's experience
that taught me how to handle stress.
When there's stress…
Pop, I'm back.
MASHLE BURNEDEAD
Why? Why do you have to break the door
every time you come in, Mashle?
Because I'm not sure
whether I should push or pull.
How many years have you been living here?
So I'm trying to find a solution.
But you still broke it, didn't you?
Sorry, Pop. I'll fix it.
Never mind, since you've apologized.
He's always compliant
after making mistakes.
You got it the wrong way!
Strange. It won't fit.
You got to turn it a little!
Huh? What?
It won't work!
I can't stop?
Ah!
Sorry, Pop. I'll fix it.
Mashle, have you finished
your training today?
Of course.
Well, Pop.
I've been thinking about one thing.
Why do you make me keep working out?
You…
You are not like the others.
Unlike other people,
you can't use magic at all.
So at least…
We'll talk about it some other time.
I need to go out now.
Guard our house well.
Don't break the door again.
Yeah, I already know how to fix it.
Why don't you learn
how to open it in the first place?
Should I push or pull?
Pull! You pull!
Anyway, I'm heading out.
I know I've told you this
countless times, but still…
Don't go to the city when I'm not around.
I won't.
That's good. Good boy, Mashle.
I'll be on my way then.
Have a good trip.
Sorry, Pop.
I have to do this.
Magic.
More magic.
People can still do many things
with a swing of their hands.
I'll take seven of the special puff.
Welcome!
Heck!
I crushed them because I was too excited.
But coins don't usually bend
when you squeeze them with bare hands.
Sorry, I'll fix them right now.
Fix them…
Sorry about this.
Wait.
It's… terrifying!
Sorry about the wait, here.
Thank you very much.
Hey, did you see that?
He doesn't have it on his face,
or anywhere else.
No way! He really doesn't!
Unbelievable!
Sir, are you…
Ah, nothing. Thanks for visiting.
This year's Divine Visionary
is Rayne Ames, a second year student
at the famous Easton Magic Academy.
He has top performance
at the academy this year.
Whoever awarded with this title
cannot only be elevated
to the rank of the nobility,
-but will also receive a scholarship of one billion Lond.
-Oh, how nice.
-Furthermore, they will have internal access
-What a talented guy.
-to the highest legal authority,
-Compared with them,
-the Bureau of Magic.
-I can only waste my life
-They are expected to have a bright future
-in a place
-in the authorities.
-like this.
Please… Please spare me.
I just nicked something.
Are you kidding me?
It's the scums like you
who give me more work to do.
I'll have to make you regret what you did
so that you won't cause me trouble again.
D-Don't! Please!
What? I'm busy.
What? There's an unmarked brat
on the street?
I wonder why those folks are so riled up.
Don't go to the city when I'm not around.
Sorry, Pop.
But I didn't come here in vain.
After all, I got the goblin cream puffs.
Yummy. Yummy. Yum…
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Look what you've done!
I'm an officer on duty here!
VODKA 90% ABV
I'm a magic police officer here
to protect you ordinary people!
Don't you have any gratitude?
I only got pennies
every month for the work I do!
How about I take my stress out
on you, kid?
Do you want a cream puff?
You sound pretty miserable.
Are you pitying me?
With a cream puff that's already chewed?
What do you mean by giving me
a cream puff that's half eaten?
Do you want an indirect kiss?
Do you fancy me?
Are you looking for trouble with me?
Do you know I represent the authorities?
And how are you going to
pay for my uniform?
What?
I'm very sorry. I'll wash your clothes
and return them to you.
I don't even have any clothes now!
It's all your fault!
What did you do to me? Huh?
What is it, Terry?
Mr. Brad, this guy…
Don't yell for such petty things.
But why are you half naked?
BRAD COLEMAN
No! It's this brat who…
It's him?
The unmarked brat from the report?
But how can he stuff himself
with cream puff at a time like this?
Hey, you over there!
Please excuse my boy!
This will be a bit of a hassle.
But now is my chance to hit something big.
Go after them!
Idiot!
I've told you not to go into the city.
How many times have I said that?
I'm really sorry. It won't happen again.
He looks upset
and he's acknowledged his mistakes.
I can't stay mad at him.
Well then,
as a punishment,
you'll repeat
this morning's training session.
Okay.
This cream puff is for you, Pop.
Thank you.
Please.
Thanks, Pop.
What a compliant kid.
Aren't kids his age
supposed to be more impulsive,
have arguments and fights with parents,
and gradually grow a stronger bond
with their parents?
But he's so obedient.
I feel like I'm getting off too easy.
He's reached the age
at which he'd want to leave home?
For all this time, I stay away from people
and live a secluded life
in the forest for Mashle.
But now, the magic police
have learned his existence.
I must find a way…
That is…
Hey, old man. Where is that brat?
I got trouble.
The training only takes five minutes
if I put my heart into it.
Okay, time to get back
for more cream puffs.
Cream as the cream in cream puff.
Puff as the puff in cream puff.
Cream puff as the cream puff in…
Should I push or pull?
Whatever.
Old man, you know what's up with that brat
and you hid him here, right?
Do you know what makes the magic
in our world flourishing?
It's because we have cleaned
the lowly blood
that has no magic power from our society.
That's a necessary sacrifice
to keep our society running.
Let me be more specific.
People who can't use magic
don't deserve to survive.
No, I should say
they should never have been born.
Spit it out! Where is he?
I have no idea what you are talking about.
Hiding unmarked people
is a serious crime, old man.
Give him to me now.
I refuse.
To be honest, if you cooperate
and give that brat to me,
I might let you off the hook.
I will… I'll never tell.
Why can't you do something
as simple as that?
I'm sorry.
Your magic power is weak
and you are so stupid.
We don't need a useless child like you
in our family.
I'm sorry.
Hey! You screwed up something so simple.
You are so useless!
I… I'm sorry!
I can hardly find someone worse than you.
I was never a bright kid
when I was little.
As I grew older, I encountered
failure after failure.
You failed again! You are fired!
How can you even stand to be alive?
I would've killed myself if I were you.
I was never needed by anyone.
And I've thought about taking my own life.
I should just…
This child has no mark.
Did they abandon you
because you have no mark?
We share the same fate.
At that moment,
I felt needed
for the first time in my life.
I made a promise then,
that even though
we are not biologically related,
even though the whole world rejects us,
I would still be his father.
Old man! Tell me where he is now!
Run, Mashle!
You old fool!
Hey! That means
he must be somewhere close! Find him!
Yes!
Run, Mashle!
Damn it! You old fool!
Please let my voice reach him.
Shut up, you!
You have to live
even if you are all alone in this world.
For me, you are the only…
Run! Run for your life! Mashle!
You stubborn old thing!
You'll regret this.
You brat! How dare you…
Two uniforms in the same day.
Why? Why didn't you run away, Mashle?
Because you are my family.
My only family.
Pop, please forgive my stubbornness.
But now…
Go to hell, all of you.
This is interesting.
You can't even use magic.
How are you going to fight me?
Stupid brat. Mr. Brad used to work
in the Bureau of Magic's Security Force.
Even the regular Mages there
are no match for him.
It's a joke that a low-born brat
without any magic power
thinks he has a chance against Mr. Brad.
I can finish you within three second.
That's the magic he used
to drive off the dragons
back in his days in the Security Force!
I never thought
I'd have the honor to witness it!
Eat this! Nalcompas!
Mashle!
That… That brat deflected Nalcompas
with a single slap of hand?
Is it possible to
stop magic attacks with a hand?
I've driven off dragons with that magic.
It's impossible!
Not bad, brat!
Let's see what you can do with this!
The magic power is pouring out!
Does he want to destroy this whole place?
Wait, Mr. Brad! You can't!
Nalcompas Diagorus!
Damn it!
This guy…
He reduced its momentum with his knees!
How can he be so flexible?
Well then, take this!
He's even juggling it now!
And he's dribbling it like a ball!
He's making a fool of me!
Pop, can I borrow your wand?
What's he going to do?
Does he know magic?
It doesn't matter.
Some everyday magic
won't lay a scratch on me.
This is my first time
seeing someone use a wand like that.
I'll kill you if you hurt my family again.
I did make him
exercise for self-defense purposes,
but he could be that powerful?
But no matter what, it's all over now.
Even if we can drive off these people now,
only more will…
Interesting. Let's make a deal,
mushroom head.
If you do what I ask,
I'll let you two slide.
A deal?
In this country,
they pick the best student every year
to be worshipped as the one chosen by god.
And they are called Divine Visionaries.
I want you to enroll in the magic academy
and become a Divine Visionary.
Simple, isn't it?
If you get selected,
it means you are accepted by god.
And the society will accept you too.
I just want the money
and the power that comes with this title.
I'll help you on your way there,
of course.
Don't listen to him, Mashle!
He was our enemy just a minute ago!
You can be skeptical or whatever.
But if you refuse,
I'll keep hunting you for all your life.
And that means the whole country
will be hunting you.
You are a tough one, brat.
But what about your old man?
You'll be living in fear
every day in your life.
You can't even set foot outside the house.
Make your choice.
Do you want to be hunted
for the rest of your life?
Or do you want to give it all
to change your fate?
It's a deal.
Are you serious? It's a magic academy!
It's okay, Pop.
My willpower is twice
as strong as that of others.
It's not about willpower!
Besides, I want to
live a peaceful life with you.
You are such a good kid.
I just want to
live in peace with my family.
If this world doesn't even allow
something like that,
then I'll have to crush it
with my fist.
NEXT EPISODE
MASHLE BURNEDEAD AND THE MYSTERY MAZE